<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guilherme Leobas</title>
    <link>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Guilherme Leobas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enhancements to Numba&#39;s guvectorize decorator</title>
      <link>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/blog/enhancements-numba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/blog/enhancements-numba/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article originally appeared in Quansight Labs blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Work Hi, my name is Guilherme Leobas. I am currently working at @quansightai as a Software Engineer. Before joining Quansight, I was a MSc student at the Federal University of Minas Gerais (dcc/ufmg) working with compiler optimizations under the supervision of professor Fernando Magno.
As part of my work at Quansight, I have contributed to a number of open source softwares:
 Numba, a NumPy aware JIT compiler using LLVM RBC, a remote JIT compiler built on top of Numba OmniSciDB, one of the fastest SQL engine in the world PyTorch, an open source ML framework   Free time I am also an amateur triathlete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>  Benchmarks - A collection of more than 220 benchmarks used by compilers engineers to measure compiler optimizations.
  TF - A simple test framework built using bash to compile, instrument and profile benchmarks.
  cftool - Get inputs and outputs for a specific problem or contest on Codeforces or URI.
  IRView - Generate dot/pdf files of llvm IR from Sublime Text
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guilhermeleobas.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Guilherme Vieira Leobas and Fernando Magno Quintão Pereira. Semiring Optimizations: Dynamic Elision of Expressions with Identity and Absorbing Elements. OOPSLA 2020.
  Caio Lima, Junio Cezar, Guilherme Vieira Leobas, Erven Rohou and Fernando Magno Quintão Pereira. Guided Just-in-Time Specialization. Science of Computer Programming, 185, 2020.
  Fernando Magno Quintão Pereira, Guilherme Vieira Leobas and Abdoulaye Gamatié. Static Prediction of Silent Stores. ACM Transactions on Architecture and Code Optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
